obscure Peas
sorry for putting you up there the Civic
is not as nice as the Prius for this
stuff but yeah so god we got my own
driving and stop and go traffic right
here pretty nice you know it's nice the
my Civic turns below 12 miles an hour
one of the nicest things about my seven
that Lane looks like it's going faster
but yeah like being behind trucks
because if you're behind truck the ACC
is so much better because trucks are so
much smoother so this is just very
smooth I'm very satisfied with this Oh
teachers chipping right away man right
away that's the commitment that's the
commitment from the commo
army we're gonna start shipping
everything out within three days cuz we
got a ship quicker I should have cut him
behind that truck and Google nothing
nowhere this morning and it came up four
do you like little peep or this guy so
I'm listening to this guy it's all right
all right it could be accelerating a
little bit we're kind of creeping along
let me use the other well I like using
this camera get mad when you get cut off
now I couldn't be following a click on
that Chuck alright my top speed 65 come
on come on let's go it's accelerate come
on let's go
I'll talk to you about this go check it
out I got my maverick joggers on yo
reloading Pulse shit yeah I know I know
I don't drive that much you guys how do
you find checksums
it's just skill bro look at him figure
out what it is just like look at I got a
few examples get examples in a 1-bit off
well you can reverse the firmware it's
kind of an extreme way to do it
i sweet rapping on this truck what
happens if a fly I don't know bro yeah
this thing should accelerate more I
don't know alright maybe our limits are
really long
I'm a software developer now bro I'm a
dumb-dumb the CEO I just show I'm the
social media manager for coming I
all right no I'm sorry about
let's see if I can put you guys here
you're right behind that steering wheel
man we get call every time right let's
see if we can do this big turn come on
Civic got this boy we can come over time
all right everyone else is going faster
than me I'm really I'm going the speed
of this truck I'm gonna be late you know
wait am I gonna be late let's see what's
a verage salary first so my salary is $0
guys so if you're a good CEO
you really shouldn't take a salary until
your company's profitable does my Civic
have the torque limit as a higher torque
limit than yours but not much higher
it's just a nice experience following a
chunk right this is just Corbin guy I'll
slap your face bro
band now I'm too lazy to ban you proud
or dare
yes how's money well I'm blame I don't
know what you do away
thanks bro like I gotta cut him boring
companies great man could tilt the
steering wheel and put the phone on my -
can I do that
is there a button for this guy's
terrible I'm over Corbin I mean you
shouldn't say he's terrible we're still
not in the mood right now so but I got
you guys in one hand I want to change
the music
Oh self-driving cars don't give you
three hands common army you could buy
all the merch Oh can you deaf a slap off
for band questions yeah oh hang on I
gonna drive your cycle
now when you face the vents the chap -
no sorry Bros Africa cut in
I know what
you
oh yeah check out that dashboard
experience of the same boat as me
Wallace change music I'll start with
that
what
really cutting okay we got
just doing my daily mix one let's see
what we got Oh moving mountains ode we
will bury ourselves why aren't i running
a midnight black IAM actually have a
midnight black e on with me how long did
it take me to learn Python one day bros
check out midnight black
why don't I just keep periscoping I mean
we can I don't know I wish I had a
fitter with it I found some duct tape
but prop you guys behind the duct tape
Oh
decent that's decent all right we got
something yeah I'm doing a fireside chat
today nope good bro being a follower is
a powerful political statement that's
why I will turn it off I'll sacrifice my
comfort for the quality moving out you
really can't see anything there what I
think it acts matic the verge gave up on
me all the verbs all oh man oh god what
will I do if the tech press has a
negative opinion of me got any advice to
young people wanting to learn computer
security thought it's a waste of time
the whole industry sucks
what Civic gym we're using is a touring
this is a 2016 touring oh yeah oh yeah
we're going a little fast now going 1900
miles an hour guys this is what driving
is boring that's why you need
self-driving car when will your car park
itself it does love you guys that was
actually pretty good that's something
pretty terrible
well the phone fit in the visor got a
motorcycle gonna have to hold it
military motorcycles I don't know about
that
advice on learning see I don't know man
Security's a waste of time just go hack
shit man like I would never call it
security yeah that kind of works
[Music]
but now I can't read what you guys are
saying no I don't like being in this
Lane Bros I think I'm gonna get over can
make some moves up not back I already
made moves I can't make moves now I wish
I had a lidar on the roof I could see
everything let me do this merge no is it
better to train an area yeah kind of I
don't know we haven't to be honest guys
we haven't a new model in a while so no
training helps no okay I got to the air
conditioner back on it's too hot in here
where are we headed today we're go to a
fireside chat in Oakland you know you
guys said you've tried but you know what
I think we're gonna make all up and over
Lane line there I think we're gonna make
all common yawns come with Paris
yes we learn Python
FBI probe I'm not worried about that bro
they have their own problems this is a
memo yesterday got some problems YouTube
what about YouTube YouTube put it on the
EON there for us I don't know about that
should be looking at we're driving too
much mandatory pop-up live periscope
that's right
you build fences think Macklemore does -
how often do I talk to you
turn the music down okay you hear me now
hey y'all we got the guts of cops here
god I gotta have a hand on the wheel
hand of the wheel we got cops gross we
got cops back so now we have duct tape
let's take some duct tape and stick my
phone not gonna work
all right traffic's picking off it's a
good deal I've got some duct tape just
duct tape you guys all right cool
cops love comedy I did I put the duct
tape over the microphone hey you guys
listen froze hey guys I get over in this
Lane
duct tape built civilization yeah go
we're all good bro it's everyday bro all
right well I know we're good for sound
now but we're not good for air
conditioning copies let's put speed up
here and let's cruise what's successful
more car models or better features roof
time here Brooks I do a lot for the
Scopus run open pile on your computer
you kind of katakana works like
everything coming at cattle works
it's ten degrees where are you sweaty
fireside chat browse project whose
project type wait oh wait I got an idea
I don't actually know how to use this
thing but we might be able what if I
just direct the air conditioning at my
feet
is there noise
yo you should have seen good good good
good go that we got some air
conditioning and we got no noise it's
the best of both worlds
like that movie they talk about in flux
alright cool oh it's good I look I got
some pure team pure leaf tea this
stuff's great no calories caffeine
purely
what's the worst PR su propio as a joke
you know what they honestly I learned
every lesson I know about PR from one
line at a gym class hero song and I've
got to try to remember what it is it's
uh don't tell me it's over he's like you
know if you want to see me God then I
suggest you keep my name out of your
headlines right so the truth is as long
as you're still making headlines you're
good
sit up real tall see we're gonna get
cold test and get cold feet
periscope is coming speaker pro same
commas PR I'm sitting in a self-driving
car what am I gonna do
Trump is PR I know right I mean you know
you just look you want one of the best
predictors of who's gonna win elections
is you look at Google Trends shopped I
come in here I what up always be
plugging
is your only interaction with the
government Pro the regulator's are our
friends I talk with them every weekend -
no just kidding that's a lie but not
other fun can a mini-computer with a 22
inch touchscreen work
maybe what would an accident do the Kaba
positivity you know that's what Logan
Paul taught me positivity you want to
test the like experience but not a test
well how about man
you can have somebody else buy a Tesla
take the Tesla badge off stick stick a
Ford logo on there and then it's like
the same
what about Windex y'all cleaning it up
yo I don't know if I can talk about it
Tesla experience is high we're anti-hype
I'm over hype hype is played out you
guys being duct tape for that vent it
works great all news is good news bad
news but it's not actually what a lot of
people think it is I don't know guys
like the PRS you ever see how PewDiePie
talks about he calls it the PRS and Wham
and you know there's a reason that he
does that and it's because wait hang on
I gotta figure out where I'm going here
on sec you know what it would be great
if this thing was actually self-driving
car it could actually take me to places
and not just stay in the lane like a
shitty linking system
somebody should really work on that and
you want to know anyone who works at
Kaname I
now they gonna work on that I heard
that's what I heard I heard it's coming
soon - yeah right changing lanes is
incredibly stressful
that was super stressful I just have to
change the cost like four lanes that was
super stressful you guys it's super
cruise control yeah I know how's the new
model coming yeah you know soon - yeah
Taylor should be the first car on Mars
I think it's targeted to orbit Mars I
mean I would say that it makes it to
Mars if it crashes on Mars
what's dangerous can be like the crypto
guards even that stuff
for level four you will need to handle
pedestrian detection yes - I think Lola
five is possible without a G I don't
know what a GI means why not do all
counties instead of employees we need
some employees families are okay calming
eyes the first I'm not going to Mars bro
no like you have to make it there's some
what attacked like if you crash there's
like a little digging on the bumper I
think that's okay but I think this turns
beyond the torque limit Oh anymore dorks
with our double torque you can do it
they had still not coded safe limits
right kind of standing vicarious is AG I
know about that it's gonna be streamed
or recorded I don't pay attention to
what Apple's doing to be honest like to
cook is a brilliant executor if you want
a slightly better iPhone every year then
you're gonna get that but if you want
anything new and you do SoundCloud
tracks check out nice I wrote a nice as
a nice it's pretty cut up there's police
visible in point four miles ways thank
you for having my back I love you ways
we are going the long speed limit so the
police shouldn't be bothering me
if different groups develop shit and try
to put it together now the truth is it's
gonna be a joint model yeah I know the
chips the iPhone eights are crazy good
um I have an iPhone X the second best
purchase the last year top purchase of
my macbook
if Steve was still alive if any would
join come I strongly doubt it now I mean
like the truth is the company's you've
heard about they're big they're not like
oh come oh please detection I really
want to do that we have big things
planned it out hello alright we have
seven point six miles to crews on this
road let's get over the Middle Ages I
want to yell at her geez
my the only guys behind the ideas
decision-making no just a front man you
know it's kind of like think about a
band right I'm like the frontman but you
know it's always like some guy in the
back who actually writes the songs it
never gets any credit so comments
probably like that everything will merge
and kill off Wow
so driving Savi's I don't care I know
that people do that that needs the PD
you know the business development if you
want to do that I'm not doing that I
mean I'd have to build a really big
vertical if I wanted to not just own
trucking but also own the holes of shit
that I was pulling right now the BD is
really bad because if you truly want to
be a maverick you can't depend on other
people because then other people can
stop you
how do you merge common army
contributions it's common profitable
clothes we've been PR S&S NPR's not not
not not the PR but PR core requests
why do you take control of the steering
room when I don't like what the car is
doing pickups bro yeah now I think
there's too much crossover and the
pickup audience in the comedy another
thing too is they don't come with these
features standard like be Accord and a
bunch of Toyotas now have these features
standard and that's what we have to be
his company i if we want to sell
millions of units so we could be a
million strong army
blockchain car
I see those brown
we got heartbreaking up ahead
heartbreaking pretty happy
good job system do that better than I
would pull requests okay how do you get
your employees yeah give me give me a
job at come AI most of them emailing
know you got the Toyota support guy
that's all we got we swipe on this five
some of them
we do have hoodies left in the HQ but
they're not for sale what happened to
the comma I see a multi-camera
multi-camera coming what I think attest
is in the Waldo problem announcement
I'll believe it when I see it v2v is a
joke b2v is a joke and the blockchain is
certainly not necessary for it I really
don't know if you're trying to trigger
me and if you are I'm triggered you win
the veto be the enemy is the dumbest
idea I've ever heard you know the color
are the EO and hezbi today it looks at
the brake lights in the car in front of
us in this case it's a Ford f-150 what
would it take to do a private setup what
do you mean a private setup
the police there's a lot of police don't
be a real police thing to do in Auckland
Mercedes
yeah they're self-driving stuff is
disappointing all those numbers came out
your feet of you with the police
no no nothing will make turning your
super into not a super it will make it
easier to support if you turn your
Subaru if you go to a Toyota dealership
and trade in your Subaru for a Toyota
then it'll make it easier to be
supported um where am I headed I'm going
to a fireside chat in Auckland if this
place called circuit bridge or circuit
launch circuit launch in Oakland you
guys can actually come if you want if
you're nearby I'm just gonna talk
periscope shit but try to be a little
more coherent say I have my laptop
you've got a few slides you know well I
put my head on this - well when there's
a motorcycle or what I'm like within you
know I feel like I'd have under a second
to react to something yeah I saw the
Phantom a guy crash I don't know man
what time is the chat at it's in 12
minutes
22 inch comedy gods yeah I got Kalyan
spinning spinning coming yawns yeah no
no we're not good I'm not good with the
PRS you know P ox
how many react developers we got we got
two I heard more if you want to come
here and develop react we hire two more
level for motorcycle detection now
inside the motorcycle detection is
difficult I think does it okay it's just
kind of a like you know it's just scared
enough driving a motorcycle let's make
sure to give him space this giant
motorcycle am i supplying the cars were
ready player one their cars what news
interviewer is Tristan news like stop
viewing the news as like they're trying
to convey facts just view it as
entertainment and like it's kind of like
being roasted on a late night comedy
show
oh no the late-night comedy show took my
words out of context yeah they're a
comedy show right the news is
entertainment
now if it's all entertainment it's not
facts if you want facts going to go Curt
about this app last night called citizen
it's like decentralized crime-fighting
app I'm really excited about it I'm
excited to go periscopes and crimes if
we open source to react I mean look at
open source come out of this here
probably great Panda update y'all got
one right here guys I've got a great
panda right in this bag here Oh yo yo
this thing is nice gross this thing is
nice
watchdog for your phone
okay on this turn right now right all
right I am Turk and turn limit exceeded
yeah so our Civic actually doesn't have
that much more torque than your Civic it
is very moderately more why is the GPS
the phone not enough for localization
it's all the antennas grow well I show
you I have a crepe hand installed in
this car I could show do you want to get
out and there's a construction zone here
construction zone combined with Botts
dots combined with poorly marked Road
soon as great panda ships all right okay
awesome
for how many Toyota's have we sold no
the great fans of an injection-molded
they're printed the new cleaning case is
nicer though a injection well the kids
are nice too but yeah we're gonna switch
over to that in a bit injection molded
cases for the white pandas an order of
10,000 made
two point seven months shreya is crying
on sale for $20 that's a good deal for
the future why do people care about the
cases I don't really know the injection
molding case was actually a nightmare to
do doing injection molding stuff is just
I don't know maybe I just don't have
experience with it they're gonna get
that around a tailgate applause how many
3d printers that we ran through we have
we have an army of them we've seen
pictures on Twitter I like to of broken
I'm pretty reliable
so our XM 200 stuff the support from the
company now actually really this is a
positive this year is all about
positivity man will people Hogan Paul
have shown me the way for positivity
injection-molding it's just hard to
prototype is the problem and like you
know that people make them older in
China so we got to do the Chinese it's
gotta like get on a plane and come here
on a plane
all right it could be it could be better
right here a little upset with all the
piles performance right now okay
it's a little way phrase does it guy we
got Bob stops and like a non-existent
left lane
release the 3d print files now when I
couldn't do that shirts yes shirt to fly
in for us
I'm sure to flying we could sell Malloy
midnight Lackey on midnight black are
the only thing in our inventory that's
selling men and I don't know why such a
nice product they're so good
it's a commie I sweat pants yeah well we
got I got my maverick joggers on right
now more police and police out Imperial
to metric
what about Imperial to metric sell some
flamethrowers I'm not selling
flamethrowers rose
it's bad enough getting this shit
through customs
got to cut out the radar I'm sure knows
exactly how fast that car is going oh
you used to say am I kind of like that
doesn't say anymore
oh I got to get off here
PRS
exit 36
my photo fires a chat heigen Oh Oh doing
crazy during job interviews
dude like people who try to like suck up
to me like that's gonna help you at all
like I only care if you know the right
answers just suck up to me by knowing
the right answers and knowing things not
knowing things offends me I mean I'm not
knowing things but like honestly here's
what gets you in a comedy I interview
you'll say something that isn't right
I'll explain why it's not right and then
ten minutes later you won't incorporate
that new information and then the
interviews oh no I'm not that mean to
people it's more like like really what
I'm looking for interviews or are people
gonna think with me I look for this on
dates - like I like people who think
with me should you work for the NSA
coming nah bro I mean you can know your
government job don't really pay well
and like you're part of like a sketchy
state apparatus that should die
you also have a meme question no that
means whole question no that one I know
the one where the guy talks about head I
was Burning Man last week what's wrong
with knowing things and sucking up I
don't really mind sucking up but like
the knowing things is the important part
of that I'd actually rather someone like
told me I was an idiot and like knew
more things that me then you're
definitely hired you know less things
than me well then maybe you're not hired
I like to hire people who know more
things I mean how do you handle
disagreements where I end up being
incorrect I try my best to handle them
well I'm we rolling about a lot of stuff
guys I mean is all right it's part of
saying a lot of stuff I just try to be
right next time right there's no like
there's no the way I view the world is
like it doesn't matter like there's an
actual correct answer and the correct
answer is on behalf of nature right like
nature provides you the correct answer
if you get the wrong answer you're just
an idiot right like there's no guide
that went wrong all the time
at least I try to do I have a reality
distortion field I don't know man I feel
like the whole world is a reality
distortion field and I try to keep it
like reality I mean yeah the confidence
is important right but it's not like
it's not like actually confidence and
you're like the worst thing is fake
confidence right like being not
confident when you don't really know
it's good I don't know the common please
get stock options of course all right
I'm somewhere bros somewhere all right
let's see is this a parking spot oh yeah
we got a parking spot oh files you do
that for we're somewhere cool you know
what they say I'm right on time how many
interview requests resumes we get a lot
of interview requests most of them are
crap what's a trait we look for in an
employee we really look for two things
intelligence and motivation if you are
both intelligent and motivated I don't
care about much else I mean know some
physics like know some no high school
physics no like high school computer
architecture literally stuff you should
learn in high school now if you want to
work for free we probably aren't gonna
offer you a job
all right in somewhere me lock my what
if you show up in a three-piece suit and
tell me I'm dumb I mean I'll probably
like we'll probably like laugh about it
over like lunch
we're at the fireside chat now
I don't know there might be people
inside you don't wanna be scoping so I
might have to turn you guys off but
thank you for joining me this far we are
in Oakland at circuit launch if you want
to show up cheers yes no honestly if you
contribute I mean that's another great
way to get hired if you're out there and
you make contributions that are like